Hello friends, welcome to the channel.
In today's video, we are going to
see the results of ICC Lombard General Insurance.
I feel that
for any insurance company, as
I told you, its net premium
income is its bread and butter
business and that is what we should look at.
Yes, if we look at the net premium, then the
net premium income is Rs 3000.87 crore
in this quarter, which is Rs 3726 crore in the previous quarter,
which is big.
If we talk about net profit, then
its net profit is Rs 390 crore
in this quarter, which was Rs 436 crore in the previous quarter
and Rs
349 crore in the same quarter last year.
If we look at it on a quarterly basis, then
we are seeing a drop of 10%
in their profit and if we
look at it on a yearly basis, then the
net profit is Rs 11.75%, which is big. The
result of any insurance company is
relief, it is relief not like our regular company.  There are
many classes etc. in it, so
if you
want to see the result or the flow,
then by pausing the video you
can see the complete details here
because if I start
discussing each point then this will become a very long
video, so that is why
I am starting this entire video for you with the
complete
result here, you
can access the video and see it here,
segment revenue, segment bazaar income is
given here,
you can also see segment bazaar operating profit here, so
this video is
informative, so do
not forget to like the video and subscribe to the channel,
Jai Hind